// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "By which company was JavaScript created?",
  answer: "Netscope",
  options: [
    "Bell Labs",
    "Netscope",
    "IBM",
    "Apple"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "The interpreter for JavaScript is?",
  answer: "Client",
  options: [ 
    " Client",
    "Object",
    "Both A & B",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Which of these is the feature of JavaScript?",
  answer: "Lightweight",
  options: [
    "Lightweight",
    "Netscape",
    "Function",
    " Script"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "Is JavaScript case sensitive?",
  answer: "Yes",
  options: [
    "Yes",
    "NO"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "Who invented JavaScript?",
  answer: "Brendan Eich",
  options: [
    "Steve Jobs",
    "Brendan Eich",
    "Rajiv Gandhi",
    "Harry Potter"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "When was JavaScript first appeared?",
  answer: "1995",
  options: [
    "1995",
    "1996",
    "1943",
    "1999"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "What is JavaScript's extension?",
  answer: ".js",
  options: [
    ".sj",
    ".js",
    ".html",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "In how many ways can JavaScript be written by?",
  answer: "3",
  options: [
    "1",
    "2",
    "3",
    "4"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "Which HTML tag used to declare internal JavaScript?",
  answer: "Script",
  options: [
    "Link",
    "Script",
    "Style",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Which of these specifies the type of list in CSS?",
  answer: "Li",
  options: [
    "Li",
    "List-style-type",
    "UL",
    "List"
  ]
},
// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
]